Hello everyone! Ayato Nishimori, the blue sky I wanted to see
Yuya Kudo
Cocona Yoshimoto
and Iho Aoki.
This time, we are going to play
Private Clothes Check Bingo!
Yay!
Bingo!
This time, we are going to play bingo while checking out the members' personal clothes.
The first place winner will get a prize?
I heard?
Let's have a look at our outfits and play bingo!
Okay, Yuma.
What's today's key?
The black denim God dress.
The zipper here.
I thought it was so cute.
The back of the dress is open, so it makes your legs look longer.
I'm wearing a staggered ribbon blouse, a long black skirt, and thick-soled boots.
I wear ribbon blouses quite a lot, like during auditions, and during auditions, I'm trying to make the judges remember me.
I wear this ribbon blouse every time I audition, and I wore these shoes. Yes, I did.
I had a pair of black ones, with a little bit of an adult look and an open thumbhole.
The thumbhole is open, so you can see a little bit of your thumb.
They make you look a little longer.
I mean, it looks like you're gonna be out in a meadow. I'd love to hear your thoughts on this, but I'm just wondering how confident you are.
I'd like to know how confident you are... about yourself... about the colors you seem to come in all the time.
I'm not sure because I've become more respectful of this lately, but I'm not sure I'm confident about this, I'm not sure I'm confident about this.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it because I'm usually looking at everyone else's.
I'm not so sure about this one, but I'm sure I'll be fine.
I'm hoping that you'll be able to write something about blue one-piece dresses and whatnot.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm sure it's a good idea.
I'm sure it's convenient if you don't open the denim shorts in the middle.
I'm not sure if I'm wearing my own clothes or not, but I'm going to try it on.
I also wanted to have a girl with me.
I also like to wear pearl hair accessories, and I wish some of them were transparent.
I've also written about a certain member who wears eccentric socks. I'm the one who writes about the strange socks, and I'm also the one who identifies certain members of the group.
I'm not even going to allow you to see me today.
Okay, next, Yua-chan!
I thought there might be a lot of people wearing blue shirts since it's spring now.
I put it in the middle.
White sneakers
Yes, I'm sure they're there.
Pink? Powder pink is popular in spring. Powder pink? Is that the model info?
I remember. What's the name of the color? Powder? They're character socks, but they're cute when you take them off, even if your clothes are fashionable.
I'm sure there are a lot of them out there, so I'm a little confident about this one.
Next is Cocona.
I was wondering if any of you have a pair of thick sneakers.
Yes, I do!
I also changed the pink pants because the photographer was wearing them.
Serious
I changed it to serious.
I'm aiming for first place.
I'm serious about Aichi, too.
You're lying.
But I thought there might be some sparkles around here.
Sparkles.
I'm hoping for this row.
Maybe the Aichi duo will wear miso katsu.
Or maybe someone will wear Uminchi T-shirts out of respect for Okinawa...
Like this.
Pointing at specific members, like here, or Mii Yaegashi.
I'm Mii-san. You'll never get it right if you don't come.
Yes, that's right.
Why?
Why doesn't Mii Yaegashi wear a hatchet?
That's right.
Yeah, that's not good.
So we have to draw lots.
I see.
Let's draw lots like this.
Let's go!
I'll draw the raffle.
The ball?Balls.
Who's there? Who's there?
Let's see what you're drinking.
Okay, first up is the goat.
And now, let's welcome our first goat, A-chan, with her cool moonwalk.
Ready, goat?
You're so cool!
You're so cool.
Oh!
Thank you.
Goat!
Thank you for your sudden and reckless decision.
Let me check out your fashion.
What's the point?
Straight book.
Jazz.
I thought they were short and herb-like.
I came here with a choice.
Who says I'm going in a circle?
Where do you fit in?
In the middle, in the middle.
Jazz dress.
I was just wondering if there was something in there.
Yes, sir.
Do you have socks on?
You have to look at his socks.
What?
That's disgusting.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're just like Yuna.
Huh? Do you personally think that's bizarre?
Uh, Jack?
Well, I don't know.
Why not? No.
But it's not what I was going for.
I was going for this.
You don't have an eccentricity section? Don't we have an eccentric section?
Are you still there?
Black boots.
Oh, girl?
I thought I wrote the same thing.
Oh, two.
One.
That's a pretty open one, isn't it?
The middle one's open. It's strong.
There was only one left.
Anybody see any sparkles?
Do you think there is?
No, but Toa-chan is.
You're different.
It's so unexpected.
But you look really good in short hair.
Yes, you're so cute.
Thank you, Toa-chan!
Now let's go to the second one.
Who is it?
Okay, please.
There you go.
Nana Shiogama.
Okay, the second one is Nana Shiogama.
Please come in as a gas station attendant.
Ready, Nana-chan?
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Clothes Clothes Thank you very much
Wait against the clothes
Clothes. Wow.
I hit it. I hit it. I hit it.
First of all, what's the point of the clothes? Clothes?
These arrived yesterday.
This arrived yesterday, too.
It's cute. It's cute. So cute! So cute!
Oh, I see. This outfit was given to me by a teacher when I retired from club activities.
The teacher gave it to me when I retired.
Stylish, isn't it? Stylish.
Shall we open it?
What do you think? A black dress.
I brought back Nanachan.
Thinking of her? Yes, I did.
Wasn't there? No?
I was hoping for a bit more.
I was hoping you'd get her a "whammy" T-shirt.
A "whimsy" T-shirt? Yeah.
T-shirt?
I bought it in Okinawa. I don't know.
You know, there's a T-shirt that says "sea slug" on it.
It's called "Uminchi"?
Nana, what a surprise.
But it's black.
There aren't many black ones.
Lighter.
Right.
It's a lesson uniform.
Nice try. Nice try.
I'm here in my lesson clothes.
Okay, then.
Coconaco's.
Who's wearing denim shorts?
Here it is.
Den
Yuzu.
Okay, third one, Yuzu Ito.
Please come in with your super cool walk.
Seino
Yuzu!
Why is he doing this?
Oh, cool! Cool!
Cool!
That's so cool!You look cool.
I'm back to Yuzu.
That was cool.
First of all, what was the point of today?
The point?
I made it look like spring.
Inside and white.
The rest is simple.
Rings
Gotty ring
Gottsume ring
Round?
Can I make it round?
Yes!
What color are your shoes, Yuzu?
They're pretty white, aren't they?
There's white in them!
I can write!
Yes!
Can we do it?
It's just a skirt. It's not that interesting.
I made it flared.
White.
Flares?
Flares.
Yay!
Oh, my God!
It's open!
That's great.
That's OK.
I'll be sad if I can't contribute anything.
Good luck with this one. Good luck with this one.
Good luck with this one.
Good luck.
Let's see.
Do you want to pull a UFO?
Yes, sir.
I'll take this one.
Who is it?
Yuriya Miyakoshi.
What will she wear?
It's always a different image.
But it's denim.
Oh, denim!
So much denim!
Yuriya Miyakoshi
Like a gal
Please come in!
Seino
Yuriya-chan!
Oh?
What do you mean?
You're in the middle.
It was very simple today.
Simple! I'm so surprised!
What do you think? Is it there?
Yes, it's there!
Yes, there is!
There's glitter and stuff.
But, it's a top.
Too bad.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, where's the top!
Where's the top?
There it is!
There it is! There it is!
Is this denim blue?
Yes!
Blue is so hard to find.
Isn't it pretty?
I'm losing it.
Blue?
Blue!
It's a circle.
On the other hand, if you want to check out my outfit...
I dare you to keep it simple.
It's like the leader of the fashion team.
It's like the leader of the fashion world.
Can you put in a little good style?
Yes! It's simple, but it looks good.
Then pull it back. Thank you.
Ta-da!
Ami Kanazawa.
Yes! Me!
Here's the set of add-ons.
You're in a lesson.
You're wearing really loud socks.
I'm wearing socks.
Ami Kanazawa.
And now, our fifth student.
Ami Kanazawa, come in looking super cute.
Do a cute pose.
Ready! Ami-chan!
What?
So cute!
Cute!
It's transparent, isn't it?
It's see-through.
And I borrowed this from Nana.
You borrowed it?
I've seen you wear it. I've seen Nana wearing it.
No, but there's something I haven't seen yet.
Ami, can I see your socks?
Please.
Come on, come on, come on.
I'll do the briar.
וח
nell
I've been trying to get a hold of you, but you've been calling me "kutik".
I'm so happy it's working!
Thank goodness it's open!
I'm glad you're here.
I'm a little bitter about this...
I'm a little bitter about this... because it's important.
Okay, two more... Yamaguchi 1.
And the second one is...
Hayasaki, Suzuki...
That's low, isn't it?
Okay, Suzuki Hayasaki and Yamaguchi... please join us.
Let's do it, Super!
Come on in!
Come on in, come on in, come on in, come on in!
Thank you very much. The main point is that I like unusual clothes.
I like unusual clothes, so look at this one.
This is the point. -A simple black-and-white.
I made a simple black-and-white dress... with my feet out.
I hear you've got a little one...
I'll wear the white and white of the "Driven" blouse.
And it's a patchy pink.
I've got a ring to show you... and it's not this old pink-pink-pink color.
Oh, gold!
It's a kikin!
I know, right?
I'm a little bit tired, but I'm still happy to be here.
I'm Aya Nishimori and Cocona Yoshimoto, and we got a bingo!
I'd like to get a reward for both of us.
I wanted to get a reward for both of us. I was hoping to receive
Nemer
Who do you want it from?
remembers it tivi kugumi no want ardy auwaiau iya home eh appari mathbei ou rialambulance 360z
I'm waiting for the cracksете dj at the same degree of mind station Dai Athens
I'd like to get a reward from you later on.
I hope you all had a good time! We often get to shake hands and talk about our outfits, so if you have any questions about today's points, I'd be very happy to answer them!
That's all for now.
I don't know. Convenience store snacks.
That's great!
He said, "Please start with this outfit.